



+48 500 163 641





github.com/jpozarycki

ABOUT

I offer you fast-learning, never-settling worker who's experience in various fields brings fresh view and exceptional soft skills can elevate your group projects to the next level.

I am 24-years old programming enthusiast based in Szczecin, Poland. I am looking for an opportunity to start my career as a web developer and my main focus is set on Java 8, Spring Boot and Angular.

EXPERIENCE

SOCIAL MEDIA SPECIALIST

Beliani | Oct 2018 - Apr 2019

Worked with an international group of artists, programmers and marketing specialist to create and manage unique advertising campaigns on the most popular Social Media.

ENGLISH TUTOR

Władca Języków | Aug 2017 - Feb 2018

Taught English language clients ranging from 5-years old to 70-years old. Lessons were run in groups as well as individually, always with Direct Communication method.

ENGLISH, MATHEMATICS, PHYSICS TUTOR

Self-employed | Jan 2017 - Jan 2018

Run my own business and taught children English, Mathematics and Physics giving them the knowledge and skills they needed not only to succeed at school, but also in life.

SKILLS

Java 8, Spring Boot, Hibernate, Maven, REST, Angular 7, HTML, CSS3, Bootstrap, MySQL,

English C1 level, German A2 level

COURSES

#!/ALX | Oct 2018 - Jan 2019

Programming and JAVA language course

EDUCATION

WESTPOMERANIAN UNIVERSITY OF **TECHNOLOGY**

Departament of Technology and Chemical Engineering

Oct 2013 - Feb 2017 B. Sc. in Nanotechnology

INTERESTS

Fitness, programming, new technologies, philosophy, self-improvement

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

Wyrażam zgodę na przetwarzanie moich danych osobowych dla potrzeb niezbędnych do realizacji procesu rekrutacji (zgodnie z Ustawą z dnia 29.08.1997 roku o Ochronie Danych Osobowych; tekst jednolity: Dz. U. 2016 r. poz. 922).